The Dental Record UP114
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Dental Record
1987 -- 1996
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Dental Medicine
UP114
0.25 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of The Dental Record from 1987 to 1996. It was published by the Dental School to convey timely and factual information about the school to its various constituencies. Published in the winter and spring.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts University School of Dental Medicine was established in 1868 as Boston Dental College. It was incorporated into Tufts College in 1899. Although founded as a school to educate students from New England, today Tufts is renowned throughout the United States and the world as a center for academic and clinical excellence. Tufts boasts over 6,900 alumni composed of individuals from all fifty states and thirty-nine countries. The majority of the alumni outside of the USA have completed an Advanced Education Certificate program. Students receive a comprehensive education emphasizing the importance of didactic coursework, clinical experience, and practice management that prepares them to enter the work force as confident, proficient clinicians.
- The Dental Record, 1987 -- 1996; UP114.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of The Dental Record from 1987 to 1996. It was published by the Dental School to convey timely and factual information about the school to its various constituencies. Published in the winter and spring.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - The Dental Record, Winter, 1987 -- 1988; UP114.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - The Dental Record, Fall, 1989; UP114.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - The Dental Record, Winter, 1989; UP114.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - The Dental Record, Winter, 1990; UP114.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - The Dental Record, Winter, 1990 -- 1991; UP114.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - The Dental Record, Summer, 1991; UP114.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - The Dental Record, Spring, 1992; UP114.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - The Dental Record, Winter, 1993; UP114.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - The Dental Record, Winter, 1994 -- 1995; UP114.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - The Dental Record, Winter, 1996; UP114.001.001.00010 (Box 1)